http://www.nashuanutrition.com/pages/privacy-policy

My Account
Welcome to Nashua Nutrition!
Shopping Cart
Your cart is currently empty.
Continue Shopping
My Account
Welcome to Nashua Nutrition!
Privacy Policy
We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site.We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. We use cookies to identify you so we can retrieve your information so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information, like their name and email address, and unique identifiers. We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary if they have subscribed to the mail list. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings by choosing to un-subscribe. Unique identifiers are collected to verify the user's identity and for use in our record system.This site may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information and unique identifiers. Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings. Unique identifiers are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our record system. We do not sell or share your information with anyone.SecurityThis site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All data is protected using the most advanced methods available. We do not store financial information like credit card numbers or personal information like social security numbers on this site.
Links
NashCash Program
Subscribe & Save
Discounts & Coupons
Refer-A-Friend Program
FAQs
Subscribe & Save FAQs
Nash Cash FAQs
About Nashua Nutrition
Contact Us
NashCash Points Program
Subscribe & Save on Your Favorites
Daily Discounts & Coupons
At Nashua Nutrition, we offer a wide selection of healthy, high protein weight loss food that’s delicious and affordable. We also offer bariatric-friendly products used by physicians and weight loss clinics, but with the convenience of delivery right to your doorstep.
Information
About Us
Contact Us
Directions & Hours
Refer-A-Friend Program
Diet Plans
IPA Calculator
General FAQs
Sign up and be the first to get notified of our special offers and latest blog topics.
E-mail
© 2020 Nashua Nutrition. All Rights Reserved.
Terms & Conditions | Privacy Policy | Return Policy | Shipping Policy | Better Business Bureau | NashCash Terms & Conditions | CA Privacy Notice
